And in this segment, I'm going to just start paint in the background color.
And when you do a children's wall mural, you probably most likely want to always start with, like, your sky first.
You want to do your background before you get all your objects and those are--it should always be last.
So what I've got here is I've got a little bit of Benjamin Moore acrylic paint and I've got it in a--it's a flat paint.
And I've also got a cheap brush and I'm just going to kinda dry-brush it a little bit onto the wall.
And I'm not going to do way solid onto the wall.
I'm just going to start kinda tapping it on and getting the wall color on there.
And if I need to mix it down a little bit then I can always use a little bit of medium or a little bit of water to dilute it.
And I'll just keep painting on here.
I'm going to start on the edge so I can get the edge painted in against the skyline.
I'm just doing a dark hill here.
I'm trying to define the edges and then kinda just dry-brush it to fill it in a little bit.
I don't want too much paint on the wall.
And you really don't need to use a lot of paint.
You don't need a lot of paint on your brush.
You want to just kinda take it easy and then use more paint as you start filling in your details.
So right now, we're just kinda put a tiny bit of paint on there.
And this entire mural is going to kinda fade in to the wall.
It's not going to be a wall-to-wall mural so I just want to make sure that I use less paint the farther out that I go.